[Music]
hello and welcome to the junkyard love
podcast what age do we learn how to have
better
conversations at what age do we learn to
have better convers ation with ourselves
well Julie thanks so much for joining me
welcome to the junkyard love podcast I'm
happy you're here um I would love to
start with the basics I would love to
just hear kind of a bio from you so
people who haven't heard of you um they
haven't read any of your work they
haven't listen into your podcast they
they're unfamiliar with who you are I
would love to kind of give them a little
bit of a background to start with so
here's the most difficult question ever
who are
you oh what a question um first of all
thank you for inviting me I'm really
honored to be here it's it's it's going
to be fun um you know I always struggle
with that question about who am I
because I had you know you may be aware
I had and I've written about and spoken
about a radical
Awakening I had Way Way Back In
1989 and when you have a shift of
consciousness of course what happens is
you wake up to the recognition that
you're not your
story and you begin to see your life
life and your story from the more
expansive perspective you see it from
the place of the I am or the Supreme
self or Source itself or whatever you
want to call it um so all of that said
in terms of the small eye or the
personal story um I am I guess that a
spiritual coach is the best way of
putting it and um following the radical
Awakening I was directed to write books
to support people who are also going
through um cerini Awakenings and
recognizing who they are and then I was
told to start creating content and
courses and programs and um and so
essentially that's what I've been doing
since around
2007 something like that and I also run
intuitive art programs and course it's
for people that want to connect in with
the self via creating artwork
so and I also have a I have a YouTube
channel as well called talking true
where I invite guests to speak about
their radical Awakenings uh or mystical
experiences and just dive into these
topics and themes that really move
beyond the story the small story so to
speak and into the vastness uh the truth
of who we
are yeah yeah wonderful um there's
there's so much exciting stuff to unpack
in there so um I mean I I think what uh
what I would love to start with is your
lucid dream um you said it was ' 89 that
this happened to you um can you can you
describe a little bit of your mindset
before this happened to you and then
kind of what your experience in life was
afterwards you know including the The
Experience itself I would love to know
the the juicy details of what actually
happened in this lucid
dream yeah so so just to create context
cuz I think this is important um I I was
a lucid dreamer from literally I think
the moment I came out of my mother's
womb um I would have these out of body
experiences and lucid dreams and for
those that might not know a lucid dream
is when you wake up in the dream and you
realize this is a dream and I am
dreaming so you are watching The Dream
from from the state of the
witness um and and what would happen is
as soon as I'd wake up in the dream then
I'd go sometimes I'd be catapulted into
another realm of existence and I'd meet
great beings or Angelic beings or family
members who' just recently passed or or
people who'd passed and I never met
before you know and they give me
messages and so on and so forth so that
had been pretty much my whole life and I
had always felt a discontent you know I
was always looking for someone ever
since I was really young I was looking
for someone who I knew could speak to
the truth of who I was beyond the story
I couldn't have described it that way as
a kid obviously but that was what was
happening and um in 1918 so I was very
familiar with lucid dreams and all of
those things and outter body experiences
and then in
1989 um T my husband Tony and I have
been living in the Bahamas for uh eight
or nine years you know living the life
the dream life and still there was this
discontent um and um I had a back
problem and somebody said if you learn
to meditate that might help you know
because it'll help you deal with
stress and because I'd always wanted to
learn how to meditate I thought yeah
this is a great idea let me go along and
you know see if I can try meditating so
I think I went two or three times and
and and it was just horrible I I felt
like a real failure I just couldn't you
know i' closed my eyes and try and my
mind was going crazy and I just couldn't
not sit still and meditate for the life
of me and so I'd look around the room
open my eyes look around the room and
think you know how do they do it you
know how they can they sit so still and
so anyway um that happened yeah two or
three times and then after the third
time I thought to myself the people here
are really nice they're great you know
professional people which was important
to me um
but I just can't meditate and I won't
come back um then what happened was I
went home and that night I woke up in a
dream and you know recognize this is a
dream and I'm dreaming and I was in a
setting that was like India even though
I'd never been to India I recognized the
environment immediately and I was
walking up a hill in this rural kind of
place and there was a little low um one
level structure on the top of the hill
very simple structure and I was walking
with a group people and we were carrying
yoga mats under our arms and we walked
in the back of the hall and as soon as I
entered into this space I saw a yogi
sitting cross-legged on a low wooden
Tucket at the front of the hall he had
his eyes closed he was wearing a white
loin cloth he had a massive
belly and I recognized him immediately
as being the one I had been searching
for my entire life
and in that moment of recognition it was
like everything fell away all that
seeking energy the frustration energy
the discontent energy just completely
vanished and um and I just felt this
profound feeling of coming home and
recognition um anyway my this woman who
was with me said unroll your mat lay on
the floor and repeat the Mantra om Nam
sh so oh is a primordial stand Namar
means I bow to and Shiva is not Shiva or
Supreme Consciousness itself so with the
repetition of that mantle you're
actually saying I bow to the Lord within
me or I bow to the truth of supreme
Consciousness Consciousness which is who
and what I am so um I lay down on the
floor I close my eyes within one
repetition silent repetition of
onira I felt a tap on the top of my head
and this incredibly profound energy
began pouring through the crown and into
my body and into every single cell and I
could literally feel this energy
circulating in every cell of my body and
it was getting more and more and more
intense to the point that it was just
felt like I was going to burst into
flames or something and um so I kept
holding the mant repeating the mant my
body floated up off the ground and then
after a while when I felt I couldn't
hold it anymore I suddenly felt myself
falling through time and space and my
subtle body landed through the heart
chakra into my physical body and then I
hadn't been breathing and so I sat up in
bed and
went you know made this cute sound and
my husband woke up Anthony woke up and
he said what happened what happened and
I said I don't know but my life will
never be the same
again and that proved true that that
that was that was a prophetic uh
response because it absolutely proved
true the most um incredible things be
begun to happen and again the context
you know I was raised in the UK in a
working class
family my father was a Catholic my
mother was an agnostic on a good day and
an atheist on a bad day
and um so I had absolutely no context
for any of this I did not understand any
of what this meant I had no background
no nothing to relate to and I found out
later that what I'd been given was
shakat
di which is the transmission the it's
the transmission of the Awakening power
from a great being I found out the name
of the great being was baban nand of
lur and he uh was renowned in India for
giving
shapath and for appearing you know
bilocating and appearing in different
places at the same time and he had
actually taken mahasi he left his body I
think in the mid 60s something like that
you know when I was I mean very very
very very very young and um and yet here
here he was appearing to me and I
recognized him and from that touch then
from that point
on uh my life really was never the same
again because even though I'd always
been a lucid dreamer and and I'd also
had psychic phenomenon you know around
me all the time it was like the blood
gates open the whole thing blew up and
so I would be having the most incredible
lucid dreams and
initiations from other great beings from
diverse pths f and traditions from
angels from Lord Jesus another Mary you
know the list goes on and on and on and
um and it was literally like the way I
explain it it was like vagabanda through
his Awakening power invited all the
great beings that he knew you know into
my space and so and so you know I'd get
these profound teachings from also from
Sufi Masters that I'd never studied and
I heard about one of whom was Mrs Irina
Tweedy who's a you know she wrote the
book The Amazing book um the what's it
called the fire I forget it'll come to
me anyway she's written books about um
her time in India with a soupi master
and also I had dreams withw and B Lee um
and so and so this just continued on for
many many many years and it still
does and um yeah and so and so
everything everything about my life
changed in ways that I could you know
have never anticipated years ago you
know for example
me hosting a YouTube channel I was
always very shy contemplative kind of
mystical in nature and you know I'm
doing this work but I never anticipated
writing books or creating
content and yeah here we are yeah well
uh I think like many others I'm I'm
grateful that um you have found this
place to communicate your experiences
from such a a levelheaded perspective um
I I've listened to you have
conversations with other people you know
I mean we all know this stuff can get so
strange it can get so you know Airy to
talk about and it's difficult to to you
know ground it in a sense kind of Bring
It Back Down to Earth and go what are
you really talking about here you know
um but I feel like you you have from
what I've absorbed of your content
you've really found a way to um bring
such a great presence to it um and I'm
sure that wasn't uh wasn't quote unquote
overnight
um what what have been like the I I just
imagine this experience happened to you
this this insane lucid dream and then a
repetition of more lucid dreams I mean
what does the next day look like for you
you know like if you if you have to go
to work and you have to pay the bills
and and do these things how did you kind
of balance out these insane you know
perception changing experiences
with you know doing the dishes um yes
you know how do you how do you make
right action out of this yeah yeah and
you know and that's a really great point
but what happened was let me speak to
directly what happened directly
afterwards so you know I when I came
into my body it was 3:00 a.m. and I just
couldn't sleep because I was filled with
the most incredible energy so you know I
go into the kitchen I start cleaning and
you know emptying out cupboards and
doing all these crazy kind of deep you
know almost like spring cleaning kind of
stuff and then um you know it came time
for me to go to work so I hop in the car
and start driving to work and I all of a
sudden I had to pull over because I was
just sobbing my heart out I couldn't
control my chest was heaving and I was
just sobbing my heart out and I had to
you know pull over and collect myself
and then I start driving again and then
I'd be laughing
hysterically and um and you know I I've
always been a teacher I still am I I
teach High School I teach art and design
and that that morning of that you know
after Shak paath Awakening there I was
you know heading to school and dealing
with a grade 10 class of boys primarily
boys who used to run to class the art
class because they used to love coming
to Art and um the first thing one of
them said to me was Miss oil you need a
new pair of shoes you
know I said you know you're right I
really do I just have not time to get
some he said oh there's a there's a shoe
sale on at Mike's shoe store and so um I
heard the same message two or three
times that day and then I thought I have
to listen to this message and I went to
the shoe store and there was nothing
there but I went I realized there was a
Unity bookstore across the way and I
went in there and then looking for some
books to try and sort of Define and
describe what had happened to me because
I you know I knew it was profound but
I'd never heard of anything like it and
and um I heard this voice behind me
saying oh hi Julie and when I turned
around it was the woman from the dream
the night
before and um and she said that she had
not been in that bookstore for 10 years
or more but she got a message that
morning to come to the book store and so
so so that that I'm I'm referencing that
because that is what started to happen
so there's all of that happening in the
background and in the foreground in
terms of directives messages people
showing up things happening and all of
those things and at the same time there
I was doing my day job very grounded you
know having to deal with everything to
do with school working in very difficult
conditions you know I had I was working
under a metal roof no AC no I didn't
even have fans that were working with
you know not many supplies art supplies
um and just making the best of it but
what what would happen is I was doing a
lot of Mantra repetition in that
space um a silent repetition of the
Mantra because it was I was hearing
inside myself it it took this kind of
Life of its own so it was like I was
listening listening to the music of it
playing itself out and repeating itself
in every cell of my
being and again for context you know I
worked in a government school which is
primarily um feeds the local community
most of whom were born again Christians
or Baptists or seventh day Adventists
they were coming from Christian
perspectives so I could never have used
the language of yoga and the shaky and
energy and the chakras and all of those
things so I learned to use language that
was accessible to the students and the
staff so I'd speak about Jesus you know
Jesus told me to tell you if you know if
it came up obviously I wouldn't cross a
that's not my business um but you know I
would use that language and the but and
the thing as well is without me saying
anything I saw evidence of this awakened
power and energy in the room because I'd
have these you know big grade 10 11 12
students coming in a lot of them boys
and they come to my desk and go like
this at
lunchtime miss all can I stay in the
room because it my spirit feels very
happy here but it's nice and quiet in
here you know another time a boy was
cleaning a board he had a wet cloth I'd
asked him to help me put up a display he
was cleaning a board he's going
on
on and that's so far outside of his kind
of lexican in terms of his his his
language and I knew that there was this
transmission that was happening and it
was so far beyond the mind but I saw I
just kept seeing evidence of it and
hearing evidence of it from what the
students were saying about how they felt
inside that space and also in terms of
their artwork because I'd
see visual images of the Awakening power
and I still do you know I still I you
know I work I work now in in in an
international school so there's more of
a you know a mix in terms of where
students are coming from but I'll see
lotus flowers I'll see arm signs I'll
see you know doves I'll see peacock
feathers and I'm not speaking to them
about the awaiting power the chakras or
anything you know at all we're just
having these openend inquiries and
creating you know artwork that speaks to
what they're feeling
inside so so it's been the most
incredible um Revelation you know in
terms of actually what happens when you
receive um an authentic an authentic
Awakening yeah it's so interesting to
think of um you know you received the
shocky pot and then you almost have uh a
continuous flow of that energy that's
with you all the time and of course it's
going to affect the people around you I
think uh you know a lot of people have
been to certain environments where you
don't it's kind of beyond words you
can't really intellectualize it but
there's just something that feels really
like spiritually en I ing here you know
and synchronicities seem to be plentiful
in these places I've been to um uh
Fairfield Iowa um it is where there's a
college for Transcendental Meditation
there and I went
there I in October so I spent a few days
there and I felt that I was I don't know
that my feet ever touched the ground the
whole time I I feel like I was floating
around everywhere I was just like in
this all my conversations seemed exactly
how they should have been um I was just
like looking everybody was looking me
deeply in the eyes and I was returning
the favor and um there was just
something about that that environment
that was really um felt right and it
felt that I wasn't fighting against much
um but they have twice a day they have
these these two giant domes where
everybody meditates twice a day um
there's hundreds of people who do it and
so I think that has something um some
sort of effect on it um yeah so it's
interesting to to be able to create
these environments you know but um
so what do you uh what is your do you
have a daily meditation practice now I
mean how do
you how do you integrate this this
knowledge and this wisdom that that you
have do you have an intentional practice
um do you take like if you're still
getting loose a dreams do you wake up in
the morning you Journal them do you need
to sit with them um I guess I'm curious
about both your meditation practice and
your integration of these kind of
continuously happening Shak Depot
experiences yeah so um what happened was
pretty soon after getting shed p and
just as a way of trying to process I
started writing in a journal and and I
was really guided to do that so um I
started journaling I think almost from
way back you know when when I it first
happened and then specifically when I
was dealing with the Shadow and doing
Shadow work you know which again for
context I've never heard of Shadow work
I had no clue what that was I'd never
done counceling as a kid or anything so
I was thrown into that um when I was
living in an asham when I went to the
asham in India that was related to Bagan
chinander my husband and I were invited
there to um to be staffed to go on there
stuffs how long sorry how long after the
dream did you end up going over to the
to the Asher that was so I had the dream
in
1989 and I my husband and I went to the
asham in 20
one I think it was so it was quite a
long time so I had this massive
honeymoon period so to speak of these
incredible experiences you know these
great beings from every path faith and
tradition and then I went we went to the
asham and I you know I wasn't assuming
anything you know but I kind of I guess
hoped that it would that those
experiences would get bigger and broader
and more kind of profound and instead I
was thrown into this
really intense
darkness and um you know it kind of
happened very organically but it was so
obvious and clear what I was being
called to do and um what happened was
when I started to recognize and and just
to kind of give the the details I was um
I was assigned to work with the
logistics Department which would oversee
programs and there' be a lot of people
coming to programs yoga meditation
programs and so and so forth and so I
was assigned to doing the logistics I
was there was a team of about five or
six of us and one morning this young
woman who had recently been assigned to
the department asked me if I would help
her set up something for a program that
was happening and I said yes absolutely
let me just finish this document that I
was writing up I was you know writing
out the kind of the the format for a
program that was going to happen later
in the week I said let me just save it
close it so I don't lose it and and she
just wasn't happy with that response and
she she kind of coiled up like a big cat
started you know cursing and cursing at
me and dropping F Bombs all over the
place and it just shook me to my core I
just I was so stunned I couldn't believe
it and um anyway I stepped outside for a
minute and leaned against the the
building and I thought to myself how is
it
possible that such an angry person could
be in the Ash and as that thought came
up this absolutely really intense kind
of dark energy started to come up and I
had this sickening recognition that the
angry person was me she was just
reflecting what I tried to sort of push
down throughout my whole life so um I
just saw everything I just saw it
clearly but I didn't know what to do
with that because i' never you know as I
said never done counseling didn't have a
clue what the shadow was
anything but um the next day I was doing
I was helping out in the library there
was this incredible library at the asham
that had the most amazing books from
every path and I was kind of walking up
and down and dusting you know and this
book literally bounced off the sh there
was nobody else around this book bounced
off the shelf and landed at my
feet so I picked it up and the the book
was by Mrs Irene Ina Tweedy and it was
called Chasm of fire never heard of it
didn't know Mrs Irena Tweedy was I had
no idea but anyway I knew the book was
for me I knew there was a message so I
signed it out took it back to my room I
open it up and there's a little kind of
preface about her and her backstory was
that her husband died when she was in a
early 50s or something like that and she
was so distraught and she was kind of on
a spiritual CR and she found out about a
Sufi master that lived in India he was a
Sufi Guru and so she went she made plans
to go to to visit him and spend time
with him and she thought when she went
she wanted him to teach her or show her
God and she said instead he forced her
to look at the deepest darkest places
within her and it almost killed her when
I read that in the preface I knew
that that was what was happening in
terms of you know what had just been
revealed to me in in in you know that
episode and so um so then I just started
doing self- inquiry and saying okay I'm
ready to do the work I will dive into
this and do whatever it takes but I need
some guidance about how to do it do have
a clue so then I kept getting these kind
of um prompts you know to do
self-enquiry
and to look at that make a list of the
people that I really admire and what
their qualities were make a list of the
people that I really didn't like and
write their
negatives and then see that you know
both of these uh aspects were also
within me and then look at why for
example uh would I hold myself back in
situation or um you know try and sort of
protect myself and you know whatever lab
the label the negative uh was speaking
to what what you know why did I do that
so I really started doing this indepth
um self inquiry around the Shadow and
that lasted some time so you know both
of those things had been going on I was
writing all the beautiful dreams you
know then I get to the asham and then
I'm detailing all of the Shadow
work and um I did that for quite a while
and that really really helped then and
of course at the time I didn't know that
I'd be writing books books you know and
so I've often gone into the journals to
be able to reacate myself with what I
was going through at a certain period of
time so that's that's kind of the
backstory but to to get to the point of
what you're saying about meditation is
the main thing is is that I had been a
Seeker for close to 30 years and I was
very Ardent I was very disciplined doing
the meditation practices chanting and
doing my japper and reading and doing
all those things and then I think it was
around
2016 I just got sick and tired of the
whole seeking game it and it wasn't like
it was
a it wasn't this kind of position I was
taking it just became clear I had this
clear moment where I saw that seeking
itself was the
obstacle and that seeking have to go so
I dropped everything I dropped doing the
all the practices all the meditation
everything the chanting
everything and the only thing that had
any kind of resonance or appeal was to
just go as deeply into the silence as I
could possibly go within my own
being and that you know happened
throughout the day when I was teaching
so so even before I'd say something and
it's still true today before words is
spoken How Deeply into the silence is it
possible to go you know into this place
prior to you know words arising you know
what do you another impossible question
what do you mean by going deeply into
the silence I I wonder if the the way
you think of it is kind of the the way
that I think about it within my own
relationship with silence what do you
mean by
that what I mean is you know first of
all connecting in obviously inside
yourself rather than being kind of outer
focused and obviously when you're out of
focused what's happening is there's a
narrative that's running all the time
right oh look the sky we're going to
have a storm or this is happening or
that's happening or there's often even a
story going on there's a narrative going
on when you're having a conversation
with someone so so you know all of that
um meditation practices help with all of
that because they help you kind of
refine the mind and let go of as many
thoughts as you may have had prior to
starting meditation so so that's kind of
the backstory right but now what happens
is after a period of time what happens
is you become more inner focused so your
focus is inwards rather than outer
directed and then going into that
silence within yourself prior to the
movement of any thought so you what
you'll notice is when a thought arises
let's say you know you have a thought oh
my God you know my hair looks a mess
today or I need to get haircut or
whatever there's a place that prior to
that thought arising that's silence
silent there's a space between
thoughts if you notice especially when
you're meditating there's a space always
between one thought or rising and then
subsiding and another thought rising
subsiding and that space is silence
itself because the place from which
thoughts arise and suide is is the self
is Source itself is
silence um or what however you want to
to describe that so so that was kind of
if you can call it a practice that was
what was happening so so I became very
um I guess familiar I don't know how to
put it but but that was that's the place
that I go into and live
from um even when I'm
working that makes sense yeah no no it
it definitely does it's uh it's this
space so much so much farther before the
story you know it's interesting the
story thing uh when we have Awakenings
we awaken to the fact that we even have
had a story we're so far far we're so
far into our story and living out as our
story and we're the character in this
thing and there's so many layers of it I
mean it takes uh just a long time to
back up and and even be acting from a
place that's not of our continuous story
and it's I mean I don't for a lot of us
I don't know how permanent it really is
I think it's a continuous
effort in a lot of ways um wow yeah I
feel like I have so many so many
questions you bring up so many amazing
um um subjects I I wonder more so so
what called you to write write
specifically books um was was
this was there like one book that came
very clearly you had intuitive guidance
like oh I need to write about this
specific subject and then it just kept
happening because you have is it nine
books or is there is there more than
nine I have I have SI I have six books
and then I have three guided journals um
so so that's a really great question
because let me just say I had absolutely
no interest intention or goal of ever
being a writer you know I'd always loved
writing as a kid and you know I and I
used to do pretty well um at high school
and so and so forth and I passed exams
in uh in English literature and language
and and all that but I had no that
wasn't part of my sort of goal not that
I had a goal so to speak but um what
happened was in 19 let me let me get it
right in uh no
2007 2007 I had a lucid dream with a
great being with a master Yogi and um
she just kind of walked up to me and she
said when are you writing the
book and I said to what am I supposed to
write about and she just looks at me as
if to say come on you know don't be such
a and then and then she just turns
around on her heels and she starts
walking away and then she looks over her
shoulder and it was just this throwaway
comment and she looks at me and she says
it's important to understand your own
journey and then she wops up so um I you
know I wake up from that dream
uh I'm lying in bed the next morning and
I'm
thinking because because she asked me I
would absolutely do it you know but I I
said this kind of prayer out loud and I
said there's absolutely no way I'm going
to write a book if it comes from ego I
don't want anything to do with it it has
to flow it has to be given
otherwise it's not happening and then I
just went about my day and just forgot
all about it and I I think it was about
3 weeks later my husband and I were we
were doing a house sit we um were
invited to look after this beautiful
house overlooking the ocean um on Grand
Bahama Island and we were taking care of
this dog this old dog beautiful old dog
and so um I took the dog out for a walk
early one morning came back made some
coffee sat on the patio and I'm just
looking over the Palm frons looking at
the ocean and then all of a sudden I
start hearing in this book or the words
let's just say being spoken and so I
just grabbed a pen and a and a piece of
paper and started writing everything
down and that's how the book was given
it was I was he it was like I
was I was hearing it it was being
downloaded from the from the Supreme
self or Source
itself um and so I just wrote everything
down and then I thought okay what do I
do now you know I a clue and as these of
things often happen I had a friend who I
you know I'd done a reading with him a
couple times self-purpose readings and
so and then he wrote back and said um
you know I had this I keep having this
idea that you should write a book and if
you're looking at writing a book you
should maybe look at smashwords because
it's you know it's a platform you can
upload books you know it's for
independent Publishers and it's easy to
use so he kind of sent me all the
details without me having to even
research it and and that and from there
on uh you know that started the whole
thing and that was really how every
single one of the books was was kind of
birthed so to speak did do you
see how has this changed your
perspective on uh
synchronicity is is synchronicity see is
that a a big word in your experience
um as in like you get this little idea
and you don't exactly know how it's
going to happen or play itself out but
you trust that it will and then suddenly
a person calls you and they have the
thing you've been thinking about or you
run into someone and they're like yeah
here's this exact I to me that seems
like synchronicity
um do do you notice that I mean since
your initial big lucid dream Awakening
in ' 89 or maybe it was before do you
notice that synchronicity plays a huge
role in in your in your life now or how
do you see the word synchronicity I
suppose um I I wouldn't say it's any
bigger than it was when I was really
really young because I was living always
living in that way and from that space
because I would hear things or I'd have
a I'd have a prompt to do something and
then it would show up so I really always
believed that and knew that that was
authentic you know I mean one one story
I do tell is um you know I had a I had a
difficult upbringing because there was
you know six kids in a small house um
you know with parents that weren't
making much money and it was very noisy
it was really hard to study and I was
having to take care of my brothers and
sisters because I was the second
oldest and um so it was really really
hard and I failed two of my exams I
needed to uh we were doing uh GCS
General certificate in SEC secondary
education I needed to pass six of those
in order to go onto a more advanced
courses similar to AP you know advanced
level courses I failed two of those and
I just thought that's it and I can't go
to college and I knew I'd always wanted
to be a teacher from from very young I
knew that that was what I was going to
do um so anyway I failed because I
couldn't you know it was an impossible
environment to study in and but one day
I you know went to school after I got
the results feeling very depressed and I
was just sitting in the student lounge
and I just got this message straight
away go and speak to the English teacher
or the professor or whoever it was um
and see if you can do your retakes at
the same time you're doing the advanced
courses it hadn't even occurred to me to
do that so I didn't even question it I
just stood up went and spoke to the
professor he said of course you can do
it let's sign you want let's get it you
know you can do it do your retakes and
so I did and thankfully I passed those
but you know if I hadn't heard that
prompt or if I hadn't believed in kind
of the authenticity of that
prompt you know I would never never have
been you know been able to go to college
so so that that's always always always
been with me and um you know I know
synchronicity the the term itself you
know has a certain quotation favor and
meaning and so on and so forth but for
me it's always about
about connecting him with Grace and
being open to receive these messages and
then of course when we receive these
messages from Source itself or the
mystery or whatever you want to call it
then it cannot help but manifest in the
outer because you know what happens in
the outer is a
manifestation of your response to what
you've been given and so of course this
magic it's a very sort of magical fluid
expansive way of living once you you
know once you get the small eye or the
mind out of the way which you intend to
analyze constrain you know run it by 10
other people before you take action and
all of those things and I just have
never have never done that I just trust
it so implicitly I just move right into
action and then the outcomes speak for
themselves yeah that's that's well said
I I really like where he went with that
I
um it's been an interesting thing uh
have you ever heard of the book there's
a book called The Celestine prophecies
have you ever heard of that book yes yes
yeah um I I I love like that that kind
of uh input on on synchronistic living
and um just kind of like the the magic
of it all and and I think that I I found
myself in various times of my life I
find myself in those pockets of it's
like just a non-doing action just
everything is kind of happening and I'm
meeting this person and had um a few
months back uh it was actually right
before I went to to Fairfield Iowa um
where the Transcendental Meditation uh
experience was happening I I was walking
around I was kind of just in my head
about whatever you know just just
overanalyzing and just just thinking a
lot really was listening to trying to
listen to a meditation lecture as I was
walking and I remember thinking as I
turned the corner at the end of this
Trail by my house um I remember thinking
like gez you know if if God or whoever
if Source or whatever is trying to show
me signs I wish they would be a little
more clear you know I think I just I was
trying to I was basically thinking to
myself I think I'm getting signs but I'm
unable to decipher them or I'm getting
in my way or you know whatever I'm going
on in this story in my head turning this
corner and then within less than 60
seconds I'm walking and uh in this guy
he like kind of leans over and I took my
airpod out and he's like hey do you have
a second to talk about uh uh to talk
about Jesus Christ or to talk about um
the gospel or something and it was just
so interesting the I was just thinking I
wish I would have clear signs if I could
just have a more clear sign and then I
ended up you know regardless of the
context I ended up just having a
wonderful um connection and discussion
with this guy for like an hour just we
just stood there and talked and um he
was saying a lot of things that really
resonated with what I was already
thinking about and um and then it kind
of led to a couple weeks of me just
feeling floaty and and and Airy and and
um so I don't know I'm just I'm very
fascinated that's why I asked I'm just
very fascinated by these these moments
of kind of synchronistic living and um
the fact that sometimes it feels that
I'm not living uh in alignment with that
and I don't notice until I fall into it
again I go oh okay now I'm now I'm
listening to that voice a little bit
more than I have been these last few
weeks or or whatever so um yeah I
suppose uh so so in your experience when
you talk to these people with with
Awakenings how how different does your
day-to-day lived experience seem to be
than other people because it it sounds
like you have been kind of you know
having a relationship with this
intuitive path your whole life in some
so some senses but I imagine you on on
talking true you probably talk with
plenty of people
who didn't didn't have these sorts of
experiences or ways of thinking until
they had a sudden Awakening um you know
later in life or you know a lot of times
trauma or or pain is what brings us to
these things brings us to our knees so
to say um so I don't know how do you how
do you parse I guess your experience of
of having these gifts from a young age
versus other people who have you know
sudden Awakenings that their mid 20s or
their 30s or 40s or or
whatever um yeah I mean it's it's it is
different because um and remember that
you know 1989 is a long time ago it's so
I've been I'm fairly well practiced in
terms of integrating what what happened
and what I was given um because it did
it as I said it did ramp things up um
but you know one of the one of the great
things about my experience is that I was
always teaching so I was always having
you know even if I had the most
incredibly amazing lucid dreams with
angels and initiations and all kinds of
stuff happening I'd still have to get up
in the morning morning and go to work
and to deal with whatever I was dealing
with so so all of that has kept me very
very grounded and really able to use
language that um isn't woooo and is is
natural and um there's a sort of
Connecting Point for people and and what
I found with with those those guests
that have come on the show is if they
had let say they had a calini Awakening
six months ago or a year ago whatever
then it's it obviously it is still very
fresh and very new and everything can be
a little bit like mindblowing and
they're not quite sure what to do with
it and they're not quite sure how to
integrate it and and so I can I can
create this safe space that allows them
to be able to speak from their undirect
experience and then also be able be able
to offer um you know tangible support
rather done something that's a little
bit kind of woo
woo or out there because he's still you
know unless you've been born into a very
wealthy family you don't ever have to
work you can sit under a palm tree for
example um you know we all have to we
all have to be able to uh communicate
and and be in the world and live live
live in a way that is authentic to our
nature and not get to too kind of high
high in the clouds you know which as we
know is all about spiritual bypassing
and I've talked about that a few times
too where you know there can be a
tendency to like try and meditate
everything away and that works for a
while but it doesn't work long
term so I don't know whe I don't know
whe that answers the question but
um yeah I mean I can you know I can
really tell if somebody is let's just
say fresh out of a calini Awakening for
example or you know it happened a long
time time ago because there is a
seasoning that happens
um yeah yeah I'm glad you spoke to that
because I um you know I mean I still
have my ups and downs for sure there
there's certain days where I feel very
clear and I feel very
um I I I I feel that I I'm in the role
holding that space for other people in
some senses and then there's other days
where I'm um as as as our our mutual
friend has said Brett Spirit um I I too
am very much in process um I I had my
initial
Awakening six seven years ago and
um now I I have so much love for you
know I watch you know my YouTube
algorithm will will spit me out my
Kundalini Awakening experience and it's
someone just talking for 15 minutes
minutes and um and I understand what
they're saying entirely but I also
understand that if someone saw this who
doesn't isn't familiar with the terms or
Awakening or whatever they might be like
well what is going on with this person
they're saying a lot of pretty intense
stuff you know but um I I see it on the
other side of oh I I entirely understand
what you're going through um you're in
some time you're probably going
to alter your the way you say these
sorts of things um the way that you
communicate with the world um because
it's just such an intense you know the
the self is just completely Stripped
Away and it's you're you're ground of
where you have acted from and where you
have
um basically where you exist from is
just like the bottom drops out in a
sense and you kind of have to create a
new uh way of perceiving the world and
sometimes it can be very intense and it
can be very um yeah W woo woo is is a
perfect word for it so there there's a
lot of there's a lot of integration that
that takes place um do you see the world
of I look at guys like Brett spirit in
in in things that you're doing where
you're offering space and you're holding
space do you see a
bigger version of this do you see you
know in the next 10 years is it going to
be a very normal part of a lot of
people's conversations like oh you
you've had an Awakening and and uh
here's where this conversations takes
place because now we have YouTube and
and podcast and they seem kind of of
like
these um
uh I I I don't know they seem like they
stand so far against and so far
different than worlds of of going to a
counselor going to a psychologist um uh
learning about these things in school
reading you know Buddhist texts in
school or or whatever it is there's kind
of this whole new thing forming with
podcasts and YouTube and social media um
I don't know I guess as I'm rambling on
here I apologize to form a question I
guess where where do you see in the next
10 years or so the work that you're
doing um do do you see it continuing to
kind of Ripple out do you see more
people sprouting up as teachers do you
see more people Awakening um in in
coming to YouTube and podcast for
answers that suppose I like to pick your
brain on that yeah sure I mean I think
there's definitely a refining that's
been happening because again compared to
what the world was like when when I
first had my Awakening or you know when
I was really young when I was looking
for kind of answers and so on and so
forth you couldn't find it very much of
anything and now of course there's
there's so much on YouTube but one of
the problems that I see is there are so
many people presenting as you know
calini experts or teachers or
gurus um but don't necessarily have the
the grounding or the experience or the
lineage you know one of the one of the
things that I know that babad nand of
Ganesh always has said is that there
needs to be a lineage so if you have a
teacher that is claiming to be able to
give Shakti paath hini Awakening I would
just question you know who is your
teacher and who is your teacher's
teacher um because it's important to
have that grounding and that kind of
lineage behind behind a person
if you're going to be working with them
so so there's that you have to kind of
watch out for and just make sure that
the person that you're working with if
if you're opting to work with somebody
um that it's authentic and they're not
just speaking about something they've
read in a book you know because I see I
do see some of that um
online so there's all of that and I
would say too um cerini Awakenings does
not then mean that you throw out you
know Psychotherapy or kind of Orthodox
counseling because there's a place for
that too um you know and if you can find
somebody who's had their own Awakening
that's even better or at least find
somebody who's sympathetic to
understanding the place that you're
coming from um so it's not like that
they're you know sort of M mutually
exclusive they're not but I think
there's definitely an upsurge in the
numbers of people that are going through
their own Awakenings whether they call
it a calini Awakening or a Christ
Consciousness Awakening or whatever the
turn is it's essentially the same thing
you know um and there is a
disintegration you know a lot of people
think uh an Awakening will make them a
more improved version of who they
already think they
are and it's the direct opposite because
it's a really destructive process you
know as you said it kind of takes the
ground away from under your
feet and you are left in this space of
recognizing you're not the story um but
kind of being able to integrate and
really you know understand who you are
beyond the story does does take time and
you also are thrown into this space of
of having to become comfortable with the
not knowing because you know with the
what the mindset we're always taught
through formal education and University
and whatever and training at work
whatever we're doing we're always taught
to present as if we know you know we
know what the story is we know who we
are we know what our background is we
know about that training and um
Spiritual Awakening is the direct
opposite of that it's about the
recognition that really you don't know
anything and it Source
itself that that informs
or speaks to whatever you need to know
in any given moment and of course again
I'm not discounting formal training or
university degrees Master's phds or
whatever all of that has its place but
it's h it has its place with respect to
the relative and the relative you know
is speaking to the story of who you are
you know we have to we have to have our
education degrees and all of that with
respect to presenting in the world and
you know finding jobs and all of those
things but again all of that is relative
to the story and the truth of who you
are your true nature is prior in the
story and it it is infinite and it's
supremely intelligent so so the more you
trust that and lean into the not knowing
the more you're able to
receive these gifts of synchronicity
these gifts of insight these intuitive
messages and
you know kind of um
manifestations that appear in your
life yeah yeah uh becoming more more in
tune with uh voices that are trying to
speak to you do
you have psych has psychedelics played a
role in your um in your journey at all
no no I just never felt
any interest or there's there was never
any need for me to try psychedelics
because I was always having a
sounds like it
yeah yeah yeah I I ask um I asked
because I always Terence petta um
Terence petta Alan Watson I mean all
these philosophers of sorts would would
basically kind of talk about the the way
of being a conscious participant in this
in this whole thing here is having a
self- dropping away experience and a lot
of times that is psychedelics that's a
you know look at guys like Romos that
was kind of his opening into being who
who we all know him to be now um was
having a psychedelic experiencing
realizing I'm I'm not my body I'm not my
job I'm not these things and those
implications just started this domino
effect of you know what what everybody
knows of rahas today um and so I you
know I I wonder if if we come from a
lineage
of ritual experiences that would intend
Al um challenge the self or or um show
us that we are at least more than the
self and then you know having some sort
of in integration process I um I read
this book The ucini and Mysteries and
they talk about all these rituals and
people would take these Journeys and
they would drink this you know iasa type
medicine and they would have a a Deb
thems and then um you know come out on
the other side you're you're you're a
different person um it's I just think
it's so fascinating to think that you
know regardless of the initial kind of
switch flipping or or dream that happens
or psychedelic experience or whatever
the initial thing is we now have YouTube
and podcasts and and these people
talking from their own truth um as as
kind of guiding hands
towards like like leading us back into
ourselves I just I I just find it so
fascinating that I can be you know
mowing my lawn with headphones in
listening to a spiritual teacher and
have genuine like
profound experiences in where I need to
like pause mowing the lawn because I'm
experiencing this thing that has just
like I said had the had the bottom drop
out um and so it's just whereas we used
to maybe had to gone to we would have to
go to the Tibetan mountains or something
like that to experience these these
profound teachings now we could listen
to people on your podcast we could
listen to your story and go whoo like
this this um this experience is is truly
possible and it's just so so altered
altering yeah yes yeah and it's just so
readily available now I mean the in the
sort of the yogic tradition years ago
what would happen is you'd have to you
you you'd spend a long time trying to
locate an authentic Sida master of
shakat Guru and then you'd have to
travel her usually to some remote place
in India and ask if you could study with
him or her and usually the period of
studying you know with them would could
be years before they even give you
shakat and so of course all of that's
completely changed now because because
everything is just so readily available
and and so kind of instantaneous if
you're open to it and if you're ready to
receive it of course and if you're also
ready to receive the responsibility that
goes with this transmission because
there's obviously this work to be done
you have to work do the work on the
psyche and the shadow so that you don't
become
imbalanced um and then you have to be
ready to do the practices because you
know especially in the beginning there's
always the practices that you're that
you're kind of guided to do whether it's
meditation
chanting
japa mental repetition of prayers and so
on and so forth so so there is a there
is a there's a wait to that it's not
like you're given this transmission and
then your life becomes amazing and
everything just goes well for you which
is the fantasy you know it's all that
that is a big fantasy oh you know I'll
suddenly be able to sort of do whatever
or I've always wanted to do and become
famous or get rich or whatever and um
and it doesn't work it doesn't work like
that yeah yeah it'll uh yeah it will
destroy your Illusions pretty quickly
it's like yeah you're gifted uh a bunch
of work you need to to get get on the
way with like here's here's the thing
you should start start
uh you have a big to-do list that is
that is birthed that's that that's for
certain um I I would love to talk a
little bit more about your podcast I
would love to um just kind of feel just
as a fellow podcaster what has your
podcast been teaching you um what what
are you has there been anything shocking
has there um
even your guests like how do you link up
with your guests um what's what's the
magic behind being a podcast host look
like for
you well you know again I had no desire
to be a podcast host it wasn't on my
list of things at all um but what
happened was in let me think during the
pandemic was it 2020 we we were on very
severe lockdown in the Bahamas I mean it
was really severe we could not leave our
houses you know we're on lockdown for
months it's just ridiculous to even go
to the food store we could only go on
certain days of the week uh according to
the first letter of your surname and
that you know yeah it was really intense
however um what happened was a friend of
mine reached out and she said that she
was creating a
podcast and um she wanted to run
Retreats via YouTube and I was one of
the first guests that she invited and
she said so it'll be live and um I would
love you to present maybe something on
Lucid creaming or you know um developing
your Intuition or something like that
and so I just thought oh I don't know
how comfortable I am with that even
though i' written books you know I'm a
teacher and all of those things I wasn't
so sure about getting online and doing
doing this um because you know I'm still
uh contemplative in quiet but but what
happened was I said let me get back to
you so I went to my alter space my pooer
and I did pooer you know I did my prayer
work and you know invoke the great
beings that I worked with nand and said
I've been invited do I do this and the
response was yes we need your help and
so um so that was it I just wrote back
and said yes I'll do it and I thought oh
it'll be a oneoff you know I'll do one
like episode and that'll be it well it
was so popular I ended up doing I think
it was a 100 presentations or something
like that um interviews and this and
that and the other on the Buddhist
biohacker um through Retreats and so on
I found out I really loved it and then I
was invited on to other shows and
interviewed endless times and and then I
got this hit you should create your own
YouTube channel and you should interview
people who had their own Awakenings so I
didn't know what the heck I'm doing you
know I never would
so I just you know figured it out got it
started and um you know last year I was
interviewing authors from diverse
backgrounds and genres and I just wasn't
feeling it and then I got this message
it was like that was like a little
practice run and I okay now interview
people who've had near-death
experiences experiences um mystical
experiences Awakenings and um people who
are heal as and stuff like that so um
there's been a big learning curve in
terms of getting all of that set up and
how to sort of create an episode so that
you know it has as many views as as as
would make it kind of worth your while
so to
speak um so I didn't know anything about
tagging and you know had to making sure
that the title of the videos the same as
a you all of those things you know I
kind of figured out as I've gone long
but I've really really enjoyed it
because it's given me an opportunity to
be able to host and support people to
get their word out it's really about my
guests it's not about me at all it's
about them Shining Light sharing who
they are you know let letting people
find them um and just having these great
in in-depth conversations and so that
will continue for as long as I'm told to
continue and when I'm told close it down
I'll just close it done and that's how
it
goes yeah well it's it's a really cool
thing I mean from what I've absorbed of
your your podcast so far uh I feel like
holding space is is something you
beautifully do I mean you really just
just hold space for someone to just
Express themselves and feel incredibly
comfortable sharing their story um
because like like I said it's stuff is
so strange you know it's really hard
to we're we're talking in this kind of
woowoo space and we're trying to make
sense of like this thing actually
happened to me and I'm trying to parse
through it and you know it's you don't
have these sorts of conversations just
you know at at the gas station or uh you
know at work you know there's just not
the sorts of subjects that that pop up
at Christmas dinner all the time so
being able to to have a space to to
discuss them freely and kind of uh
explore what we think and and what we've
learned and um just parse our different
knowledge and experience on to one
another is just just a really beautiful
thing they've become really this type of
conversation people who have had
near-death experiences people had sudden
Awakenings become like one of my
favorite things to listen to they just
they bring me to such a a place that my
mind is always trying to hang out in all
the time anyway and so just to hear
other people expressing their truths I'm
like ah okay I'm not so crazy like I I
have these things going on and just just
a place of acceptance I spent spent a
lot of time listening to um Buddha at
the gas pump with Rick
Archer i' I just waiting to see your
name on there I feel like you would be a
fantastic guest I think you and Rick
would have a wonderful conversation um
you you've heard of that one you've
heard of Buddha at the gaspa yes I have
I think the way it works is um people
suggest to him who to have on and then
he says yes or no is the way it works
but yeah I like his show I think it's
really nice and uh this I mean obviously
I don't resonate with everybody but a
lot of the guests it's just really great
listening to to what they have to say
you know and and with respect to what
you were saying about um it's all
feeling a bit woooo I know Brent says
the same thing you know and I think
that's why he uh created his his show
but for me this is really normal it's
natural it's the way I live and I did go
through a period in the
late 80s early 90s where I was desperate
to talk to other people and find other
people find you know and and now not so
much because I I guess I don't need that
level of support in the same way you
know what I mean I guess is what what
what's happening but even even all of
that said I do love to create this safe
space for people to be able to speak
their truth and to um and to share it
because I know I know what it's like to
feel lonely or alienated because that
was certainly how I felt as a kid it was
just very painful and I remember when I
first wanted to learn how to you know do
happy yoga I could only find one book
there was only one
book available in this bookstore in the
town that I lived and to me that was
like
gold so um yeah so I'm just so happy
that it's
everything's just so out in the open now
as opposed to how it used to be yeah
definitely yeah more of us can take our
you know actual lived experience and
find others who have had similar
experience and um kind of make some
sense of it and kind of make a little
bit of a little bit of progress into
integrating it you know because it's uh
I think a lot of people have somewhat of
mystical experiences but we we don't
know what to do with it and it almost
becomes you know without the integration
without um reading a couple books
listening to other people who have had
similar
experiences I mean in just a few months
you go like did that didn't even happen
did that that crazy thing that was so
important to me for multiple weeks like
was that even a true experience you know
and so yeah I I I totally agree I just
think it's so so beautiful that we have
so many different resources forming now
to where we can um can talk about things
like subtle body without it feeling like
it's an attack on a materialistic view
of the world you you know it's I think
it's it's all
paradoxically it's all kind of existing
and and we need to be able to to I
suppose express ourselves and and talk
about our our own truth and um uh meet
other people who are who are along the
same path um I do want to uh I had a I
was thinking about the fact that you've
written you know six books and then
three um let's say nine books
um do you if if you had all your books
in front of you and you kind of Tak
going a step back do you have like a
general consensus of of the message that
that you're I mean I guess like what is
what is ultimately your message um
another kind of impossible question for
you but um what what do you think is the
through line between all all of your
books and in your podcast and in your
work like what is really trying to be
expressed do you
think
if yeah well with respect to the books
um it's the first book was really
detailing the story of Awakening and
what that was like and I know people
that have read that have you know got a
lot of benefit from it because it's
helps them support their own kind of
process through a especially through a
calini Awakening um and all the way
through the main message is to trust
yourself trust your inner knowing trust
your inner guidance you know listen to
what you're hearing
inside um lean into that lean into the
the not knowing so you know everything
I've shared in in the other books first
one an awaken life a journey of
transformation is as I said about the
Awakening and then the other books
detail lucid dreaming and you know the
importance of listening to dream
messages and being present in your life
and then with the shadow books Shadow
work books you know what is the shadow
what does that look like how does it
show up in your light how can you work
with it how can you mine the
Gold that is is is at the heart and the
depth of the darkness within you because
there's always a creative component that
comes out of this the the UN Earth thing
of the Shadow and the integration of the
Shadow so um again it's really all about
you know Having the courage to go inside
yourself and to meet and greet what you
find there and to trust it trust the
voice of it you know even if it's
uncomfortable and it's painful and it's
a message you do not want to really look
at or here you know um this this this
great um gold and treasure in in and
what you find within your own being
rather than looking outside
yourself you
now yeah yeah we we have this knack for
wanting to explore what's out there in
in the cosmos and the Galaxy and and how
far can we physically go and that's all
amazing that's all so fascinating but um
yeah if you just has turned that on
itself I mean there's an infinite
exploration in inside too and it's it's
the most fascina I spent a lot of my
time
um as some sort of musician poet um you
spent a lot of my time creating and and
that's what I one of my favorite things
to do is just kind of get lost on the
the inward journey and exploring myself
and really figure out what I think and
um you know you I stub my toe internally
too you know I I come across things I'm
like oh I didn't mean to uncover that
you know tring to deal with this thing
right now you know so um that's just
part of part of the whole Awakening
Journey um what do you what do you go
ahead go ahead again no I was G to say
yes
absolutely yeah um
uh what what do you have so Awakening as
a whole whether it's considered a
Kundalini Awakening or you know just a
general broad brush stroke of Awakening
um I guess uh
what do you have to say to people who
are Awakening um suddenly uh people
who regardless of how they got there
regardless of of where they're where
they're at with it at this moment um I
guess uh do do you have a message or
maybe even a little advice to people who
are who are waking up currently yeah I
mean one of the most helpful things that
certainly was very beneficial for me was
having a journal
because in those moments where it felt
overwhelming or I wasn't quite sure what
was happening or whatever I would write
it you know I'd write the question
what's going on or something you know i'
write something in my journal and then
do stream of Consciousness writing
around that and another little kind of
thing that really helped I was inspired
you know I got this little
download to um in those moments when I
felt you know down or depressed or
worried or whatever about what was going
on
I would write at the title uh where am I
in my life right now at the top of the
journal page and then the first image
that comes to mind I draw it and then I
do stream of Consciousness writing
around what I was being shown and it was
always so incredibly profound in terms
of you know the message the underlying
message of all of that and even Looking
Back Now into my journals years and
years ago it's just like holy M that was
just so on point and the reason it's
really effective is because by drawing
the image even if you can't draw it's
just like crappy Stickman drawing or
whatever um because you're going
straight into the imagery you're
bypassing the critical mind and then
from that image you can start doing
stream of Consciousness writing and then
you can give it a title as if it was a
movie or a book and then that speaks to
this the place place where you feel like
you're stuck or you need some insight or
you need an answer to
something uh and it's just a great
little exercise and it just it just
gives you this you know tremend
tremendous Insight in terms of what's
happening and where you are and yeah I I
like that a lot I uh I in in my own
journey I found writing and journaling
um whether it's some artistic thing that
I think I might share on the other side
or if it's just for me um sometimes I'll
I'll write and I'll just you know you
get into one of those little flow States
for a few minutes or an hour whatever it
might be sometimes you take a step back
and you reread what you wrote and you go
whoa I didn't know I thought that I
didn't know that um I didn't know that I
was really even experiencing that and so
yeah I agree with you I like that it's
it really gives us a lot of perspective
on what's really going on I like to say
my
um my thoughts my thoughts about what's
going on they get stuck in my head
cavity and they just Bounce Around in
here sometimes and sometimes I just need
a way to to get them out you know to
where I can really dissect them and and
inspect them and then make some sort of
actionable move on the other side so yes
yeah it's very simple that exercise
where am I in my life right now it's
really
easy yeah brilliant um okay cool well we
we are getting up here in time um I I
definitely want to send we're GNA have
some links down below um where we can
find more of your work um what do you
have on the horizon though what what do
you have coming up do you have some more
guest plans are you writing any books
right now what do you have going on
coming
up yeah so I'm I'm I've got a long list
of guests and now I'm getting emails
from people who've seen me on threads or
wherever they've seen me on YouTube and
asking if they can come on to the show
so that's really nice um so I've got
that that that will go on for as long as
As I said um I keep getting the message
to do it and then I'm currently in the
middle of starting another book
um I'm not clear where I'm going with
that yet so I won't go too much into the
details of it but and then I'm always
doing intuitive art work I have a whole
um you know I have a whole platform on
Fine Art America with my intuitive art
and I teach programs as well um on how
to create intuitive art you know and
again by bypassing the critical mind and
connecting with a c um and then still
teaching still working full time so I
have a full full Place yeah sounds like
a lot of people yeah a lot of people
think I just sit under a palm tree and
meditate all day that's why
connected it's the absolute opposite
believe me it's this and they say well
you know you know I I'm working
part-time and I've got you know couple
kids or whatever and you know I don't
know the time you have I'm like okay
really yeah you're like I I didn't
realize they had all this free time it
doesn't seem like it but whatever you
say yeah yeah so and I always say listen
if I can connect in with the S and do
the practices give them my schedule then
you can too it doesn't have to be a
three-hour seated practice every day
when you're peeling potatoes or cleaning
the kitchen or whatever you're doing at
home you can say your prayers repeat
your Mantra or go into the silence
within your
being that is a spiritual practice it
doesn't have to to be formal you know
cuz that's where that trips a lot of
people up you know I don't have the time
you know okay well I'm sure you clean
I'm sure you cook for yourself I'm sure
you go to the grocery you know store I'm
sure you
drive you know while you're D just see
how deeply you can go into the silence
you don't have to zone out and close
your eyes when you're driving but just
see if you can get go into that space
and watch the movement of the Mind
rather than being lost in the movement
to the mind so all of these things yeah
are I I I like to say um some form of
you know what you do is what you always
do I when I first started meditating I
was I was so obsessed with like
meditation I was still trying to
understood understand what that meant
and what that meant to me and so I
remember specifically I would travel a
lot for work and I would get through Air
Force Security and I would find a good
place to sit I'd get there early I'm
like all right I'm sitting crisscross
apple with my eyes closed and like I was
was like performing meditation in a way
um but but now it's uh you know just for
recent example you know learning
Transcendental Meditation has kind of
taken over you know so I have this
continuous Mantra and now it's just a
process of me
remembering and then going ah yeah and
then the mantra's always going it's not
like I'm intentionally now doing the
Mantra it's oh yeah I remembered that at
this moment I could tune into the Mantra
that is Contin ously moving within me
you know and so yeah totally I entirely
resonate with that you
know it's it's not so much of a let me
pencil into my schedule at exactly 10:15
a.m. I will be sitting in this spot you
know there's times where where you need
that and there's times where that's
that's part of what it is but ideally I
think uh our spiritual practice becomes
a
um tun tuning tuning frequency that we
kind of uh just have access to in a
wonderful way so yes exactly
simple yeah simple um okay Julie well
thank you so much for your time uh uh
really I'm I'm so grateful for this
thank you for um uh rolling with the
punches of my rambling questions and uh
providing providing space for me to to
kind of just uh pick your brain and
explore more more of your work um I I
I'm really looking forward to exploring
more um I want to I want to grab a
couple of your books and check those out
I'm going to continue listening to your
podcast and um just thank you so much
for all all the work that you put in and
everything you do I really appreciate it
thank you so much this has been really
great I just love these conversations
that just kind of just flow you know
it's great I love it great great Perfect
all right everybody well listeners check
out Julie stuff we have some links down
below um and if you haven't drank any
water today drink some water if you
haven't to stop for a second to love
yourself love yourselves um Explore More
Julie stuff
and we'll see you guys next episode
thank you Julie we'll be in touch thanks
bye
[Music]
bye knowledge is
power
[Music]
n